DirectX修复工具V4.0更新日志（重要更新）
新增的功能：
    新增C++修复失败时的详细错误显示功能。用户需在“选项”对话框中开启“修复失败时启用调试模式”功能，即可在C++修复失败时查看详细的错误原因，并根据提示手动修复。
    在“选项”窗口里新增“高级”选项卡。在该选项卡中可以控制修复C++的模式，默认为智能检测，其他可选项包括强制检测、默认不勾选、不提示异常、不检测；同时将原实验室内的“C++强力修复”功能和“API Sets强力修复”功能移入此处。原“高级”选项卡中的功能整体移至“注册”选项卡。
    新增了可以调整扩展连接方式的切换开关。程序默认使用非加密连接，如果因防火墙设置或其他原因导致的扩展失败，可以通过切换为加密连接来避免下载错误。
    新增一条控制C++扩展功能的命令。只要在Settings.ini文件中增加“ExtendFirst=True”命令，即可让程序在启动后自动扩展C++数据包，免去用户手动前往“选项”对话框中扩展的麻烦，也降低了普通用户将其使用的标准版、在线修复版程序扩展为增强版的难度。命令行同样支持此命令，具体语法请通过/?或/Help参数查看。
    新增了在常规修复过程中检测DirectX加速功能。如修复完成后程序检测到系统DirectX加速仍未开启，将会进行相应提示。
    新增程序更新功能。用户只需在“关于”对话框中点击更新按钮，程序即可自动搜索目前最新版本，并提示用户安装。更新成功后，程序会根据目前的C++数据包，智能扩展至最新的数据包。

改进的功能：
    优化了本程序所需.NET运行库支持情况，从V4.0版起将不再默认提供DirectX_Repair_win8_win10.exe程序，而是通过兼容模式实现DirectX Repair.exe一个程序兼容所有操作系统，减小用户的使用难度。
    更新了部分c++数据包。新版程序更新了C++2013和C++2015-2019的数据包，新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。同时支持修复C++2013在部分系统上因证书错误导致的安装失败问题。
    优化了“选项”对话框中的功能位置，原“实验室”选项卡中的项目移至“高级”选项卡，同时在实验室中新增控制程序更新的功能。
    优化了对于API Sets修复功能的支持。新的检测模式将会进行更加细致的检测，其结论将为“正常”或“异常”，不再有“可用”的情况。
    优化了快速开启/关闭Direct加速功能，除原版本已支持的DirectDraw加速外，还支持快速开启/关闭Direct3D及AGP纹理加速功能。详情请通过/?或/Help参数查看。
    优化了对于Windows XP系统的支持，新版本在XP系统上不再支持C++强力修复功能。
    优化了反馈功能。新的代码可以更好的支持用户反馈功能，避免因被防火墙等拦截而导致的发送失败。
    优化了C++强力修复失败时的错误提示。新的提示将重点突出错误提示码，避免其他提示信息干扰用户判断。
    优化了部分英语翻译。新的翻译更加准确，便于用户理解，同时实现在英文模式下无其他语言信息干扰。
    优化了对于静默模式授权的支持。新版本可支持中文文件授权。
    其他细节性改进。

修复的BUG：
    修复了一个在Windows10系统上可能导致Direct加速检测不正确的BUG。
    修复了一个导致授权信息显示异常的BUG。


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.9更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增对于显卡驱动异常的检测。在Direct加速页面，程序可以检测显卡驱动异常（包括未安装显卡驱动、驱动过旧）导致的问题，并对用户进行提示。
    新增对于简约模式修复完成后提示时间的控制功能。可通过settings.ini（Timeout=xxx）或命令行（/timeout=xxx）实现，其中xxx为数字，单位为秒，可控制修复完成后提示显示的时间。xxx最小为0，最大为99，超过99意味着程序自动修复完成后不会自动退出，必须手动退出。

改进的功能：
    更新了部分c++数据包。新版程序更新了c++2015-2019的数据包，新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。
    更新了Direct加速的实现算法。新的算法速度稍慢，但准确性较高，在绝大多数情况下可以保证与DirectX诊断工具中显示一致。新算法可以支持显卡驱动状态检测，同时保留旧算法，可通过settings.ini（AccelerationMode=Old）或命令行（/OldAccelerationMode）强制使用旧算法（Windows2000不支持新算法）。
    优化了对于c++ 2010的支持。针对c++ 2010在部分电脑修复失败的问题，提供了额外的修复支持，需在选项菜单内开启“C++强力修复”功能和“API Sets强力修复”功能。
    优化了日志文件的显示方式。新的方式将c++2015-2019与API Sets日志信息独立显示，方便用户查看修复情况。
    优化了扩展页面代码。新的代码显著提高扩展成功率，并可以提示用户网络异常，由用户选择是否忽略网络错误。
    大幅优化了程序体积。通过整合优化代码，实现程序体积大幅下降。
    更新了实验室中的错误调试模式。启用此调试模式，在c++更新失败时提供具体错误文件数量提示，方便用户判断。
    优化了部分英语翻译。新的翻译更加准确，便于用户理解。
    针对Windows 2000进行了部分优化。
    其他细节性改进。

修复的BUG：
    修复了一个在某些特殊路径下无法扩展c++数据包的BUG。
    修复了一个因文件属性异常导致的修复失败的BUG（需开启强力修复模式）。
    修复了一个程序在被调用时可能提示错误的BUG。
    修复了一个程序提示可能显示异常的BUG。
    


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.8更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增通过命令行快速开启、关闭DirectDraw加速的功能。可以通过命令行调用的方式，使DirectX修复工具快速开启、关闭DirectDraw加速，而无需显示主界面及使用鼠标操作。命令为：/EnableDirectDraw、/DisableDirectDraw。可与/passive或/quiet命令配合使用以实现自动化提示。
    新增3种对于c++检测的控制模式。新增的模式为：不检测c++，不默认勾选更新c++，不提示c++异常。增强版默认为自动修复c++异常，但当不需要修复c++时，可使用新的控制模式。不检测c++模式，意味着程序只对DirectX进行修复，即使使用增强版，也不对c++进行检测。不默认勾选更新c++，表示使用增强版修复时，在主界面“检测并修复”按钮右侧的下拉箭头不再默认勾选，需要用户自行勾选才能修复c++。不提示c++异常，是指在使用标准版或在线修复版进行修复时，即使检测到系统c++存在异常，也不提示用户升级为增强版。配置文件开启方式：在settings.ini中新增一行，命令分别是：DetectC++=False、DefaultC++=False、PromptC++=False；命令行的参数请用/?或者/help查看。
    新增1种c++更新对话框的弹出模式。默认情况下，增强版只有在检测到系统c++存在异常时才会在主界面“检测并修复”按钮右侧显示修复c++的下拉箭头，而系统c++正常时则不会显示。此设置可能会给部分用户带来困惑，使其无法区分标准版和增强版。新增一项控制命令，可以使增强版程序即使在c++正常时也强制显示下拉箭头。配置文件开启方式：在settings.ini中新增一行，命令是：ForceDisplayC++=True；命令行的参数请用/?或者/help查看。

改进的功能：
    更新了部分c++数据包。新版程序更新了c++2015/c++2017的数据包，新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。
    更新了实验室中的错误调试模式。启用此调试模式，可以在程序出现错误时给出更多的调试信息，方便确定问题所在。
    改进了程序的被调用模式。新的模式更安全，防止程序被恶意使用。
    其他细节性改进。

修复的BUG：
    修复了一个c++强力修复功能在极个别电脑上可能无法修复的BUG。
    修复了一个在Windows10系统可能无法给出正确操作提示的BUG。
    修复了一个在简约模式下提示可能显示不正常的BUG。
    修复了一个在非标准显示模式下可能导致窗体显示异常的BUG。
    修复了一个提示框标题显示异常的BUG。
    


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.7更新日志（重要更新）
新增的功能：
    新增对于DirectX 12文件的支持。d3dcompiler_47.dll属于DirectX 12相关文件，新版程序已支持对该文件的检测及修复。
    新增全新的c++扩展包。新版程序增加了c++2017的扩展包，可以修复c++2017的相关内容，可以在一定程度上提高0xc000007b错误修复的概率。
    新增c++强力修复功能。如在常规模式下无法成功修复c++，可直接在本程序的选项界面内开启强力修复功能，可大幅提高修复成功率。此功能为试验性功能，请仅在常规修复无效时再使用。
    新增API Sets强力修复功能。参照DirectX相关文件的精细修复模式，API Sets强力修复功能可以显著提高对应文件的修复成功率。此功能为试验性功能，请仅在常规修复无效时再使用。
    新增了加密的下载方式。如果常规扩展操作无法成功，可以考虑使用加密的下载链接进行扩展，以便增加成功率。启用方法是，在settings.ini文件中新增一项：SecureLink=True。在扩展页面左上角可以看到一个锁型标志，即代表目前使用加密连接。
    新增对于命令行的支持。本程序可以被命令行调用，并接受命令行中提供的参数。具体参数可在命令行中用“/help”命令查询。
    新增对于繁体中文的支持。新版程序添加了对于繁体中文的支持，同时新增支持本程序语言自动适配系统语言的功能，方便使用。
    新增了两种可以设置安全级别的方式。当本程序被设置为无人值守的自动安装模式时，可以在settings.ini文件中新增一项：ForceLowSecurity=True，此时程序将被强制设定为低安全级别模式，避免出现全部文件修复失败的问题。在settings.ini文件中新增一项：DefaultLowSecurity=True，此时程序默认的安全级别被设置为“低”，打开选项对话框可以看到“低安全级别”已被勾选（此命令只对第一次运行DirectX修复工具的电脑有效，如果电脑之前已经使用过DirectX修复工具，则默认安全级别已经被设置为“高”，此命令无法再更改）。
    新增了一种快速查看日志文件的方式。只要将日志文件log.dat拖拽到DirectX Repair.exe的图标上并运行，即可快速查看日志文件。

改进的功能：
    更新了部分c++数据包。新版程序更新了c++2015的数据包，新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。
    细化了c++数据包的修复与显示。将c++2015数据包中包含的API Sets部分独立出来，做到单独修复、单独显示，避免原先的笼统的结果显示。
    优化了c++2015对于全系列Windows系统的支持。新版程序可以针对从Windows XP至Windows 10各种系统的差异化修复，显著提高修复成功率。
    优化了程序的扩展机制。新的机制下，所有扩展文件在扩展完成后将会自动生效，直接开始修复即可，无需再像老版程序需要重新运行程序才能生效。
    优化了c++修复完成后需要重启的提示。新版程序会自动检测修复完成后是否需要重启系统，并给出相应的提示。如修复完成后程序未提示需要重启，则代表所有修复已即时生效。
    优化了全部文件修复失败时的提示。此类失败通常是由于文件校验错误产生的，通过在本程序的选项菜单里将安全级别改为“低”即可。新的提示将引导用户进行相应的设置。
    优化了部分英语翻译。新的翻译更加准确，便于用户理解。
    其他细节性改进。

修复的BUG：
    修复了一个可能导致扩展进度显示异常的BUG。
    修复了一个可能导致系统版本号检测不正确的BUG。
    修复了一个可能导致给出错误c++修复提示的BUG。



------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.5更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增全新的c++扩展包。新版程序增加支持了c++2015的扩展包，可以修复c++2015的相关内容，可以在一定程度上提高对于0xc000007b错误解决的概率。
    新增扩展功能。在“工具”菜单下“选项”对话框的“扩展”界面中，可以扩展程序的c++数据包，可将标准版及在线修复版程序直接扩展成增强版，免去了再去网上自行寻找相应版本的麻烦。同时仍保留手动下载数据包的链接，方便在无法连接网络时进行扩展。

改进的功能：
    更新了部分c++数据包。程序根据用户的反馈情况，及时更新了c++2013的程序数据包。新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。
    改进了对于管理员权限的检测与提示。新版程序将在所有的系统中均检测是否具有管理员权限，如果没有则进行相应提示，避免因缺少权限而带来的修复失败。
    改进了在部分系统上全部修复失败时的提示。程序将主动引导此类系统的用户使用低安全级别进行修复，从而避免因系统核心组件异常导致的修复失败。
    改进了更新c++文件的校验机制。新的机制可以更加智能的判断需要修复的文件，减少不必要的文件操作，提高效率。
    改进了部分英文翻译。新的翻译更加准确，方便用户理解。
    其他细节性改进。

修复的BUG：
    修复了程序在注册DirectX文件时可能卡住的BUG。
    修复了调整DirectX加速时状态显示异常的BUG。
    修复了在特殊某些路径下无法更新c++的BUG。
    修复了在某些特殊情况下c++可能更新失败的BUG。
    


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.3更新日志
改进的功能：
    优化了下载部分的代码。当使用在线修复时，新的代码可以更高效率地完成下载，节省修复时间。
    改进了捐赠界面。手机捐赠界面、网页捐赠界面、免费捐赠界面独立显示，提供更多帮助信息。

修复的BUG：
    修复了程序对c++安装情况可能给出错误提示的BUG。
    修复了程序被其他软件调用修复时可能出现异常的BUG。


------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.2更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增控制DirectX加速功能。DirectX加速功能十分重要，但部分用户的加速功能被禁用无法开启，使用本程序“选项”菜单里的小工具即可轻松解决加速被禁用的问题。
    新增全新的c++扩展包。新版程序增加了c++2013的扩展包，可以修复c++2013的相关内容，可以在一定程度上提高对于0xc000007b错误解决的概率。
    新增了版权信息显示功能。用户可以根据自身需要决定是否显示版权信息，方便将本程序内嵌使用。

改进的功能：
    更新了部分c++数据包。程序根据用户的反馈情况，及时更新了c++2012的程序数据包。新数据包兼容性更强，可以修复更多的内容。
    大幅优化了程序首次显示速度。通过对于代码结构的优化，实现了对于窗体首次显示速度的大幅提升。
    改进了修复的提示完成的框。新的提示更加人性化，方便用户执行相关操作。

修复的BUG：
    修复了部分系统下c++2012修复失败的BUG。
    修复了反馈程序显示异常的BUG。
    修复了更新c++数据包提示错误的BUG。
    修复了Windows 7系统下大字体时窗体显示异常的BUG。
    修复了Windows XP系统下简约窗体显示异常的BUG。
    修复了简约模式可能意外退出的BUG。
    

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V3.0更新日志（重要更新）
新增的功能：
    新增全新的c++扩展包。程序（仅限增强版可修复c++）可以修复更多的错误，解决更多的问题。
    新增注册指定文件夹下所有dll文件的功能。旧版本的程序只能注册系统文件夹下的dll文件，而新版本可以注册任意指定文件夹下的dll文件，方便用户对绿色版、硬盘版的程序组件进行注册。
    

改进的功能：
    针对工业软件的0xc000007b错误进行优化。针对工业软件（如3DS MAX、MAYA等）进行了大量优化，优化对64位工业软件的支持，可以显著提高修复成功的概率（较之前版本而言）。
    优化了对于Windows Blue(Windows 8.1)系统的支持。针对系统相关内容进行优化，防止程序运行时出现意外错误。
    优化了对于c++修复功能的检测与提示。修复完c++后，程序会分别检测c++的注册表和文件是否全部正确，并且给予不同样式的提示，方便用户的了解。通常情况下，c++注册表的错误不影响其他程序的运行。
    优化了程序的提示功能。如果用户使用标准版进行修复，修复完成后如果程序检测系统中的c++组件仍存在异常，则程序会自动提示用户使用增强版进行修复，免去了用户的麻烦。
    优化了反馈程序的提示功能。在发送反馈信息前给予用户提示，避免因部分安全软件的提示给用户造成困惑。
    对捐赠界面进行优化。新添加了二维码，只要用手机一扫即可快捷捐赠，免去了使用网页捐赠带来的诸如步骤繁琐、需要证书等烦恼。同时仍保留网页捐赠链接，方便没有手机客户端的用户。
    其他细节性改进。

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V2.5更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增两种全新的窗口样式。其中一种为简约模式，此时窗口将只显示最基本的内容，修复会自动进行，修复完成10秒钟后会自动退出。增加该窗口样式的目的是可以使修复工作变得更加简单快速，同时方便其他软件、游戏将本程序内嵌，即可进行无需人工参与的快速修复。开启简约模式的方法是：打开程序所在目录下的“Settings.ini”文件（如果没有可以自己创建），将其中的“FormStyle”一项的值改为“Simple”并保存即可。
    新增高级筛选功能。开启该功能后用户可以自主选择要修复的文件，避免了其他不必要的修复工作。同时，也支持通过文件进行辅助筛选，只要在程序目录下建立“Filter.dat”文件，其中的每一行写一个需要修复文件的序号即可。该功能仅针对高级用户使用，并且必须在正常窗口模式下才有效（简约模式时无效）。
    新增智能修复功能。根据目前大多数用户的实际情况，增加了智能修复，在最理想的情况下可以减少100%的在线修复下载需求，极大缩短了在线修复的耗时。智能修复功能在64位系统上的效果要明显好于32位系统。
    新增了查看任意位置日志文件的功能。只要在主程序的“文件”菜单中的“查看日志文件”菜单上单击右键，即可通过弹出的对话框查看任意位置的日志文件（仅限本程序的日志文件）。


改进的功能：
    改进错误处理能力。改进后可以进一步降低修复失败的概率。
    优化了对于Windows 8系统的支持。鉴于Windows 8系统中默认未包含.NET Framework 2.0，因此新版的程序文件夹内将包含一个DirectX_Repair_win8的特别版程序，该程序功能与通用版相同，基于.NET Framework 4.0开发，可以在Windows8系统中直接运行（其他系统如果安装了.NET Framework 4.0或更高版本也可以运行这个特别版的程序）。
    优化了日志文件的记录内容。在修复时点击“取消”按钮后也会记录日志文件，方便将来进行分析。
    改进了日志文件的部分编码方式。使用旧版程序可能无法正确显示所有的内容，而新版本可以正常显示V2.5及之前的所有版本的日志文件。
    其他细节性改进。

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V2.1更新日志
新增的功能：
    新增修改DirectX安装文件版本号功能。有部分电脑显示已安装的DirectX的版本号为0.00.00.0000，使用本软件可以修改成任意版本号（如4.09.00.0904）。请注意，修改DirectX版本号并不能真正改变你系统中已经安装的DirectX的版本。修改后只是会改变某些软件的显示。
    新增修复完成后自动退出功能。若使用在线修复，由于网速原因修复时间可能较长，用户可以到“选项”对话框中开启此功能（默认未开启）。当修复完成时，程序给予提示，如果用户不进行任何操作，10秒钟后程序会自动退出。


改进的功能：
    取消了修复完成后进行用户反馈的提示。这样可以使程序界面更清爽。
    取消了在线修复时的百分比显示。这样可以防止在部分电脑上程序停止响应。
    选项对话框的界面改进。优化了界面的显示，增加了一些提示，改进了一些选项。
    其他细节性改进。


修复的BUG：
    修复了在线修复时在某些电脑上会停止响应的BUG。修复后程序运行的稳定性将会大幅提高。
    修复了在部分电脑上某些文件会修复失败的BUG。修复后可以杜绝绝大多数的修复失败的情况。

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V2.0更新日志（重要更新）
新增的功能：
    新增在线修复功能。使用在线修复，可以使程序精简到极致的1MB，方便移动。同时仍支持离线修复，自由选择两不误。如果您无法连接到Internet，也可以手动下载离线数据包： http://blog.csdn.net/vbcom/article/details/7303410
    采用了全新的底层程序架构。新的异步多线程架构使检测、下载、修复相互独立，互不干扰，可以显著提高程序的检测修复速度。


改进的功能：
    将反馈程序融入主程序中。新的反馈程序将不再是单独的文件，而是集成于主程序中，方便用户移动，也为在线修复提供方便。
    改进了程序自我校验方式。新的校验方式从原先的显式校验变为隐式校验，程序不会再出现自我校验失败的错误，同时程序安全性较之前版本相同，并未降低。
    改进了修复失败时的提示内容。如果修复失败，程序将会提示用户以安全模式引导系统，然后进行修复。经测试，该方法对于大多数的修复失败有效。
    改进了反馈程序的弹出机制。新的机制将不会在修复完成后直接弹出用户反馈按钮，而是引导用户从帮助菜单中启动。这样做的目的是由于现在我收到的反馈太多以至于应接不暇，更换方式后进行反馈的人会减少，以便我更好的为大家服务。
    优化了选项菜单中的相关选项。由于在线修复的需要，原有的“文件检测方式”已经不再适用，改由安全级别选项代替，因此删除了此选项。由于在线修复的需要，原有的“允许使用精简版的数据包”已经不再适用，改为显式下载的百分比。
    更改了反馈程序的限制关键词。新程序不再将"DirectX"作为程序限制关键词，方便用户进行描述。
    其他细节性改进。


修复的BUG：
    修复反馈程序随机校验码异常的BUG。
    修复反馈程序错误文件异常的BUG。

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
----------------------------------------------更新分隔线----------------------------------------------------------
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX修复工具V1.2更新日志（重要更新）
新增的功能：
    新增注册DirectX组件的功能。程序在修复完成后会自动注册需要注册的组件，方便其他软件调用。
    新增允许使用精简版数据包的功能。使用精简版的数据包可以有针对性的减少程序的体积，但必须在程序“选项”中勾选“允许使用精简版的数据包”后方可使用，否则会出现自我校验失败的问题。程序默认自带的是增强版的数据包。
    新增修复失败时重新修复的功能。当修复失败时，程序会出现重新检测并修复按钮，不用退出程序即可再次修复。
    新增自动更新c++功能。由于绝大多数软件运行时需要c++的支持，并且c++的异常也会导致0xc000007b错误，因此程序在检测修复的同时，也会根据需要更新系统中的c++组件。此功能是可选功能，仅在使用增强版数据包时有效。
    新增英文语言包。该功能可以方便非汉语用户的需求。只需在程序目录下的"Language.ini"文件中将"Language=Chinese"改为"Language=English"即可。
    新增记录失败详细原因的功能。如果修复失败，则程序会记录失败的详细原因，方便日后参考及改进软件质量。
    新增反馈信息保存功能。如果反馈失败，则保存反馈信息，再下次反馈时可以直接调用，无需再次填写。


改进的功能：
    增强了多线程功能。根据CPU核心数的不同，程序最多可以支持4条线程同时运行，大大加快了修复进度。在使用“注册系统中所有dll文件”功能时尤其明显。
    优化了对于Windows 7系统的支持。由于Windows 7中的Aero特效可能会占用某些文件，新程序可以在修复时临时关闭Aero特效以保证修复效果。
    更新了反馈程序至V1.3.4418.34674。新的反馈描述更加详细，功能更加强大，提示更友好，可靠性更高。
    增强了对d3dx10_40.dll文件修复的能力。该文件可能被系统占用，新程序可以将其解除占用后再进行修复。
    改进了自我校验的算法。新的程序采用了加密的校验算法，安全性很高，速度稍慢，杜绝了莫名失败的可能性。新算法以略牺牲速度的代价换来了高的安全性和良好的兼容性。如果想提高速度，还可以到“选项”中更改为“一般校验”，校验速度可以大幅提高。
    改进了修复的核心算法。新的算法可以有效减少修复失败的可能性。
    改进了自我校验失败时的提示内容。新的提示图文并茂，方便用户查找问题。
    优化了对Windows XP系统的支持。对于Windows XP系统，将其不需要的d3dx10.dll文件换为其需要的xinput9_1_0.dll文件。同时检测用户是否具有管理员权限，如果没有则给出相应提示。
    改进了修复完成提示对话框的显示。新的对话框将使程序挂起，防止误操作。
    改进了重绘控件的代码。新代码使得控件重绘速度大幅提高。
    改进了日志文件的对齐算法。新算法使得日志文件完全对齐，方便浏览（只针对Windows 7）。
    改进了“注册系统中所有dll文件”功能对于64位系统的支持。用户可以选择是否要注册64位的dll文件。
    改进了修复失败时的提示。新的提示可以告诉用户失败的可能原因及解决办法。
    改进了反馈程序的调用方式。反馈程序不能单独运行，需要从主程序“帮助”菜单中的“用户反馈”按钮调用。
    改进了日志文件的显示方式。新的程序直接在txt文件中显示，方便用户保存及日后浏览。
    优化了对低分辨率屏幕的支持。如果用户屏幕分辨率过低，则程序会自动最大化，方便用户完整浏览本程序。
    改进了关于窗口中的字体样式。将原来的华文琥珀字体换为微软雅黑字体，提高程序显示的一致性。
    其他细节性改进。
    

修正的BUG：
    修正了自我校验失败时无法写日志文件的BUG。
    修正了修复图标显示异常的BUG。
    修正了dll右键菜单添加时路径异常的BUG。

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V4.0 (Key Updates)
New Features:
    C++ error details are available if any of C++ components is failed to be repaired. The users shall enable the function "Enable debug mode when failed" in the Form "Option" first to use this feature. Once it is enabled, the users could check the detailed information about the C++ errors, and repair them manually with assistance from the programme.
    A new tab named "Advanced" is available in the "Option" form. In this tab, users can control the mode of repairing C++ components. The default value is Intelligent, while other options such as Mandatory, Don't tick by default, Don't prompt exceptions, and Don't detect are also provided. C++ Enhanced Repairing and API Sets Enhanced Repairing are also moved from Lab tab to this tab to have consistency with other C++ features. The features provided previously in Advanced tab are moved to Registration tab.
    A new switch to change the downloading mode for extending is available. This programme will use unsecured link by default. If the downloading process is blocked by the firewall or other software, users can switch to secure link to avoid it.
    A new command is available to control the extending process of C++ components. If users add a command "ExtendFirst=True" in the File Settings.ini, the programme will automatically extend itself to the enhanced edition once it started. This feature can help the users extend their programme fast without going to the Option tab and click for several buttons. This feature is also supported in command line. Please use /? or /Help to acquire more information.
    DirectX Acceleration will be detected automatically during the normal repairing process. The programme will prompt the users if some of DirectX Acceleration is still remained disabled after repairing.
    Programme upgrade is available. The programme can upgrade to the latest version if the users click the Upgrade Button in the Form About. The programme will also extend its data packages intelligently after upgrade according to the current package status.

Improved Features:
    The dependence of required .NET runtime is optimised. From V4.0 on, this programme will no longer provide DirectX_Repair_win8_win10.exe by default. Instead, DirectX Repair.exe is designed to be compatible with all Windows OS versions to decrease the difficulty of selecting executable for new users.
    Some C++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, C++ 2013 and C++ 2015-2019 packages have been updated to the latest version. New packages have better compatibility and can fix more errors. Meanwhile, certificate errors from C++ 2013 on some systems can be repaired by this version.
    Some features in "Option" dialogue have been moved. The options in Tab Lab have been moved to Advanced Tab, and some new functions that control the upgrade process is newly added to Lab tab.
    The detection of API Sets is optimised. The new algorithm will check the files more deeply, and the results will just be OK or Error, instead of Available.
    All Direct Acceleration can be enabled or disabled instantly in command line. Except DirectDraw which has been supported in previous versions, Direct 3D and AGP Texture can also be enabled or disabled instantly by command. Please use /? or /Help to acquire more information.
    Improved the support of Windows XP OS. From V4.0 on, C++ enhanced repairing is no longer supported in this OS.
    The feedback function is improved. The new code can support feedback better, and decrease sending failure generated by firewalls.
    The tips for C++ enhanced repairing are improved. New tips will focus on the error code instead of other information which may generate influences on users. 
    Some parts of English translation are improved. The new translations are more accurate and correct, which could provide a better understanding of the programme. Meanwhile, no other languages will be shown in English mode to avoid influences on users.
    Improved the authentication for quiet mode. The new version can support authenticate to Chinese characters.
    Other detailed improvements.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug that may provide incorrect results of DirectX Acceleration on some Windows 10 OS is fixed.
    A bug that will show incorrect layout of authorization information is fixed.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.9
New Features:
    A new feature that could detect the errors in graphics card driver is added. In the page DX Acceleration, the programme can detect the errors in graphics card driver (including not installed or too old) and notify the user about the potential issues.
    Users can control the time of showing the prompts after repairing in the simple mode. This can be realized both through settings.ini (Timeout=xxx) or through command line (/timeout=xxx). xxx could be a number (unit: seconds), which will control the time of showing tips after repairing. The minimal value for xxx is 0, and the maximum is 99. If xxx exceeds 99, the programme will not exit automatically after repairing.

Improved Features:
    Some c++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, c++ 2015-2019 packages have been updated to the latest version. New packages have better compatibility and can fix more errors.
    The algorithm for detecting DX Acceleration is updated. Although the new algorithm is a little bit slower than the old one, it could be more accurate than past and provide the same results than the ones from dxdiag in most cases. The new algorithm also supports detect the errors in graphics card drivers. Meanwhile, the programme retains the old algorithm, users could force to use the old algorithm through settings.ini (AccelerationMode=Old) or through command line (/OldAccelerationMode). Please note that Windows 2000 is too old to support the new algorithm.
    The support for c++ 2010 is optimized. The programme provides extra operation for c++ 2010 due to the repairing failed in some computers. This extra operation can be activated by enabling "C++ enhanced repairing" and "API Sets enhanced repairing" in "Option" dialog.
    The log file system is optimized. In the new approach, the programme can show the results of c++2015-2019 and API Sets separately, which is easier for users to check the results.
    The code for extending is optimized. The new code can improve the success rate of extending c++ packages significantly. It can notify the network mistakes and let the users to decide if to continue.
    The size of this application drops dramatically. By optimizing the code of this programme, the size is much smaller than before.
    The option "Enable debug mode when failed" in Lab tab has been updated. The programme will provide the number of files that were fixed failed in c++ updating page if users enable this option.
    Some parts of English translation are improved. The new translations are more accurate and correct, which could provide a better understanding of the programme.
    Some optimizations are made for Windows 2000 OS.
    Other detailed improvements.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug that could cause c++ extending failed in some special paths is fixed.
    A bug which may cause repairing failure due to abnormal file attributes is fixed. To repair the files with these special attributes, please enable enhanced repairing.
    A bug that may provide wrong messages when is being called from other applications is fixed.
    A bug that may prompt incorrectly is fixed.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.8
New Features:
    New commands are available to enable or disable DirectDraw instantly from command line. Now the programme can enable or disable DirectDraw from command line without showing the main form. The new commands are: /EnableDirectDraw and /DisableDirectDraw. The new commands can be used associated with /passive or /quiet commands to perform automation tips.
    Three new control modes for c++ components are added. The new modes are: "Do not detect c++", "Do not tick repairing c++ by default", and "Do not prompt c++ exceptions". Normally, enhanced edition will repair c++ by default; however, if you do not intend to repair c++, you could use these new modes. In "Do not detect c++" mode, the programme will only repair DirectX, even though you are using enhanced edition. In "Do not tick repairing c++ by default" mode, the sub menu next to button "Check and Repair" in the main form will not be ticked by default. Users will have to tick this option manually. In "Do not prompt c++ exceptions" mode, the standard edition of programme will not notify the user to update to enhanced edition when c++ exceptions are detected. You could enable these new modes in "settings.ini" by following commands: DetectC++=False, DefaultC++=False, PromptC++=False. Please use command /? or /help to check the approaches in command line by yourself.
    A new c++ updating form pop-up mechanism is available. Normally, the enhanced edition will only show the arrow next to the button "Check and Repair" in the main form when there are some errors in c++ components. This design may confuse some users because it is difficult for them to distinguish if they are using standard edition or enhanced edition. Consequently, a new mechanism is added, in which the programme will always show this arrow regardless of whether there are errors in c++. You could enable this new mode in "settings.ini" by the following command: ForceDisplayC++=True. Please use command /? or /help to check the approaches in command line by yourself.

Improved Features:
    Some c++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, c++ 2015/c++ 2017 packages have been updated to the latest version. New packages have better compatibility and can fix more errors.
    The option "Enable debug mode when failed" in Lab tab has been updated. The programme will provide more information to address potential issues if this option is enabled.
    The response when this programme is called from other applications is renewed. This new response is safer than before and is less possible being used illegally.
    Other detailed improvements.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug that could cause c++ enhanced repairing failure is fixed. 
    A bug which may provide inaccurate tips in Windows 10 OS is fixed.
    A bug that may display wrong tips under simple mode is fixed.
    A bug that may display abnormal forms in non-standard display mode is fixed.
    A bug which will show wrong caption in some message boxes is fixed.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.7 (Key Updates)
New Features:
    New support for DirectX 12. A file named d3dcompiler_47.dll which is belonging to DirectX is now supported.
    New c++ packages are added. The programme can now support c++ 2017 redistributable packages and solve relevant problems. 
    C++ Enhanced repairing is now available. If you cannot repair c++ during normal repairing, you can go to "Tool" -> "Option" -> "Lab", and enable "C++ enhanced repairing". This function can increase the success rate significantly. Please be aware that this experimental function should only be used when normal repairing is not successful.
    API Sets enhanced repairing is now available. This enhanced mode can repair API Sets files carefully as DirectX files, which may improve the results of repairing. Please be aware that this experimental function should only be used when normal repairing is not successful.
    Encrypted downloading link is now available. If you cannot extend the programme in normal operation, you could try to use this secure downloading link. Please add a new command in "settings.ini": SecureLink=True. This function is working if you can see an icon of a lock on the extending page.
    Command line is supported. This programme can be run by command line and can accept parameters from command line. Please use the command "/help" to check available commands.
    Traditional Chinese is available now. This programme can support Traditional Chinese, and it can adapt its language to system language automatically.
    Two ways of setting security level are supported. If you add a new command in "settings.ini": ForceLowSecurity=True, the programme will be forced to run under low security to avoid unexpected errors; if you add a new command in "settings.ini": DefaultLowSecurity=True, the default value of security level for this programme is "Low". Please note that the second command mentioned above is only available for a new computer which has never run DirectX Repair before. If a computer has used DirectX Repair before, the default value of security level has already been set to "High" and cannot be modified by this command.
    A new measure of viewing logs is added. If you drag the log file "log.dat" to "DirectX Repair.exe", the programme can show the log files automatically.

Improved Features:
    Some c++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, c++ 2015 packages have been updated to the latest version. New packages have better compatibility and can fix more errors.
    Improved the repairing of some c++ packages. The repairing of c++ 2015 is now divided into c++ 2015 main part and API Sets. These two components can be repaired and shown separately to avoid any confusion.
    Promoted the support of c++ 2015 to multi operating systems. The programme can now repair the files accordingly no matter it is Windows 10 or Windows XP. This improvement can raise the repairing success rate.
    Improved the mechanism of extending. Under new mechanism, the extending files are available directly after a extending process without the needs of restarting this programme.
    Improved the tips after a c++ repairing. The programme can now intelligently detect if it is necessary to restart. If no restarting instructions are given, all the repairing which has been done is available directly.
    Improved the tips if all the files are failed to be repaired. This type of error is usually generated by wrong verification, and it can be avoided by setting the security to "Low". New tips will guide the users to make such settings.
    Some parts of English translation are improved. The new translations are more accurate and correct, which could provide a better understanding of the programme.
    Other detailed improvements.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug that may provide incorrect percentage when extending is fixed.
    A bug which may show wrong system version number is fixed.
    A bug that may provide inaccurate tips of c++ is fixed.

-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.5
New Features:
    New c++ packages are added. The programme can now support c++ 2015 redistributable packages and solve relevant problems. The rate for solving 0xc000007b problems increases due to the new packages.
    The feature of Extending is added. You can open the “Extending” page from sub-menu “Option” under the menu “Tool”. In this page, you can extend the programme with new c++ packages. It allows you to extend your Standard Edition or Online Edition to Enhanced Edition directly, without searching the Enhanced Edition from the Internet by yourself. Meanwhile, the programme still provides the link for downloading data package manually, which could be useful for the situations that Internet connection is unavailable.

Improved Features:
    Some c++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, c++ 2013 packages has updated to the latest version. New packages have better compatibility and can fix more errors.
    Messages for insufficient administrator privileges are improved. The new programme will check if you have administrator privileges before the repairing starts. A message will warn you if you do not have sufficient privileges to complete the repairing successfully in every Windows OS.
    The notification of failed repairing for all the components has been improved. New tips will guide the users to enable Low Security directly, which might avoid the failures caused by the exceptions of the core system components.
    The mechanism of checking c++ files has been improved. The new mechanism will be more intelligent when checking the files, and will require less unnecessary operations of the files.
    Some parts of English translation are improved. The new translations are more accurate and correct, which could provide a better understanding of the programme.
    Other detailed improvements.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug that the programme may get stuck is fixed.
    A bug which may show incorrect status when you are changing the DirectX Acceleration is fixed.
    A bug that the programme may not be able to update c++ in some special paths is fixed.
    A bug that c++ components might be failed to be updated in some special situations is fixed.


-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.3
Improved Features:
    The codes for downloading files are optimized. When you are using the Online Edition, new codes will download files in a higher efficiency and save your time.
    Donating page is improved. Three new separated pages which are Mobile Donation, Website Donation and Free Donation have replaced the old page. New pages are friendlier and will provide more information.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug which may give wrong information when you are updating c++ has been fixed.
    A bug which may lead to exceptions when this programme is being called by other software is fixed.


-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.2
New Features:
    A function of controlling DirectX Acceleration is added. Although DirectX Acceleration is essential for most users, someone still find that their Acceleration is disabled or not available. There is a new tool in menu “Option” which allows you to enable your Acceleration that has been disabled.
    New c++ packages are added. The programme can now support c++ 2013 redistributable packages and solve relevant problems. The rate for solving 0xc000007b problems increases in some extent due to the new packages.
    A function of showing copyright information is added. If you wish to call this programme by other software, there is a new switch for you to decide whether you want to show the copyright information of this programme before you start repairing.

Improved Features:
    Some c++ packages are updated. According to the feedbacks from some users, I update the packages of c++ 2012 to the latest version. New packages have a better compatibility and can fix more errors.
    Displaying time for first running has decreased significantly. The code structure has been optimized to improve the speed of showing the main form.
    Message box of completing has been improved. News tips are friendlier for users to operate the following steps.

Fixed Bugs:
    A bug which may cause failed updating of c++ 2012 in some computers is fixed.
    A bug that feedback form displays exceptionally is fixed.
    A bug which may provide incorrect tips of c++ updating is fixed.
    A bug which may show exceptional forms in Windows 7 when using large fonts is fixed.
    A bug which may show exceptional forms in Windows XP when enabling simple form style is fixed.
    A bug that may lead to unwilling quit when enabling simple form style is fixed.


-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
---------------------------------------------------Dividing Line-------------------------------------------------------
-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

DirectX Repair V3.0 (Key Updates)
New Features:
    New c++ packages are added. The programme (only Enhanced Edition) can now fix more errors and solve more problems in your systems.
    A function of registering files in a specific folder is added. The old versions can only register files in system folders, while the new programme allows you to register any files in any folder, which may benefit the users of using some special versions of software.

Improved Features:
    The ability of solving 0xc000007b errors in some industrial software has been optimized. The new programme makes a lot of improvements for industrial software (such as 3DS MAX, MAYA and so on), especially for 64-bit software. 
    The programme is optimized on Windows 8.1 systems. Some codes have been improved to give an excellent compatibility and avoid errors on Windows 8.1 series OS.
    Notifications of checking c++ components are improved. The programme will give separated messages of registries and files to show whether they have been repaired successfully. In normal context, it will not affect the running of other software if only registries are still exceptional after repairing.
